wttw.com 2018-06-22

# WWCI Privacy Policy | WTTW Chicago Public Media - Television and Interactive

#### (Updated: 2/22/18)

**Click or scroll for more information:**

  * What Information We Are Collecting and How We Are Collecting It
  * Personal Identification Information
  * Security Policy
  * Non-Personal Identification Information And The Use Of Cookie Technology
  * Disclosure of Personal Identification Information
  * Children's Privacy
  * Access To/Correction of Information
  * Your Acceptance of These Terms

**Please Read:**  
Window To The World Communications, Inc. (WWCI), licensee of television station WTTW/Chicago and radio station WFMT/FM, has created this "Privacy Policy" to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and security while visiting our website. We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our sites.

This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

* * *

**What Information We Are Collecting and How We Are Collecting It** Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, which serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" (IP) address. When a visitor requests a page from within the WWCI website, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed the WWCI website. We use this information to examine our traffic in the aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors. We may determine what technology is available through your browser in order to provide you with the most appropriate version of a web page.

* * *

**Personal Identification Information**  
Should you opt-in by supplying your information in an online form or donation form, from time to time we may disclose personal identification information about you as an individual user (such as, for example, your full name, street address, telephone number) to one or more third parties in order to expand our membership base and increase support for our programs. We may request personal identification information from you in connection with your use of, or participation in (i) contests, sweepstakes, games or surveys, (ii) becoming a member of WTTW or WFMT or pledging financial support, (iii) community postings such as forums, discussion groups or bulletin boards, (iv) requests for additional information in connection with other activities, services or resources we make available on our site and (v) e-mail transactions. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. We do not share e-mail addresses with any third party.

If you do provide us with personal information, we may use it to conduct the activities described above. If you identify yourself to us by sending us an e-mail with questions or comments, we may use your personal information to respond to your questions or comments. We may, at our sole discretion, either file your comments for future reference or discard the information after we have reviewed it.

* * *

If you give us your permission, we may also use personal identification information for internal marketing and promotional purposes, or on occasion, when mailing lists are made available to other organizations. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form you may receive mailings from other reputable, third party companies. If at any time you would like WWCI to discontinue using this information, you can let us know by contacting us through our Contact Form or by calling our Member and Viewer Services department. Please note, however, that under certain circumstances, if you "opt-out", you may not be eligible for certain benefits for which a name, e-mail address, telephone number or other personal identification information is needed.

**Security Policy**  
Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure both your information and our physical premises. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Our secure server software encrypts information, ensuring that all Internet transactions remain private (unless sent by an unsecured means, such as e-mail). Neither WWCI, any telephone network nor service providers are responsible for incorrect or inaccurate transcription of information or for any human error, technical malfunctions, lost-delayed data transmission, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, line failures or any telephone network, computer equipment, software, inability to access any website or on- line service or any other error or malfunction or misdirected entries.

* * *

**Non-Personal Identification Information And The Use Of Cookie Technology**  
We collect non-personal identification information through the use of "cookie" technology and/or IP address tracking. Non-personal identification information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, the operating systems, the Internet service providers and other similar information. Our system also automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our sites and about the links you may select from within our site to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online. We use such information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our sites. This way we know which areas of our sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites.

You can set your browser software to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, some parts of the WWCI website may not function properly if you do so.

* * *

**Disclosure of Personal Identification Information**  
WWC will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  1. Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on WWCI;
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of the WWCI website, or visitors to the WWCI website;
  3. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Terms of Use or the rights of third parties; and
  4. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

Third parties who provide hosting services or other day-to-day services that make possible the operation of this website may have access to information that you provide to the extent they require access to our databases to service the website. Those third parties may employ cookies which may be used to identify your preferences or recognize you if you have previously been to their website or otherwise had contact with them.

WWCI reserves the right to transfer information we have secured from you in connection with the sale of all or part of WWCI's assets. WWCI is not responsible fore any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive information. WWCI may provide links to a wide variety of other websites. WWCI is not responsible for those websites' privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. Please check with those websites to determine their privacy policy.

* * *

**Children's Privacy**  
This is a general audience website and does not knowingly collect or store personal information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child (who is under 13) has provided WWCI with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at the e-mail address or postal address listed at the bottom of this Privacy Policy if they would like this information deleted from our files. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time. Any portion of our site directed to children complies with COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). Our site may link to sites or services owned or controlled by PBS/PBS Kids, and we suggest that you review those sites’ policies to learn more about their privacy practices.

* * *

**Access To/Correction of Information**  
If you would like to review any personal information we have retained about you in our database, please send us an e-mail request for this information at [ask@wttw.com](mailto:ask@wttw.com). Once you have reviewed this information, at your request we will correct personal information about you that you state is erroneous. To request such a correction, please send an e-mail to [ask@wttw.com](mailto:ask@wttw.com).

* * *

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using the this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of this WWCI Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

This website is operated in the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, please be area that any information you provide will be transferred to the United States. By using this website you consent to this transfer.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example, through e-mail) that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

If you have any questions comments or concerns regarding this privacy policy please contact us at the following e-mail address: [ask@wttw.com](mailto:ask@wttw.com)or write us at:

WWCI  
5400 N. St. Louis Avenue  
Chicago, Illinois 60625
